/* Array holding the questions */
var quizQuestions = [
    {
    question : "What did Rick have that everybody wanted?",
    options : [
        "fame",
        "money",
        "Letters of Transit",
        "liquor"
    ],
    answer : 2
    },
    {
    question : "Who said 'play it again Sam'?",
    options : [
        "No one",
        "Ilsa",
        "Rick",
        "Victor"
    ],
    answer : 0
    },
    {
    question : "What color dress was Ilsa wearing when she and Rick were in Paris?",
    options : [
        "Green",
        "Gray",
        "Red",
        "Blue"
    ],
    answer : 3
    },
    {
    question : "Why did Ilsa leave Rick waiting at the train station?",
    options : [
        "She forgot what time the train left",
        "She got sick",
        "She was married",
        "She changed her mind"
    ],
    answer : 2
    },
    {
    question : "What line in the movie was the basis of the title of a 1995 Kevin Spacey movie?",
    options : [
        "We'll always have Paris",
        "Round up the usual suspects",
        "The Germans wore gray",
        "This is the beginning of a beautiful friendship"
    ],
    answer : 1
    },
    {
    question : "Who was reputed to be the first choice to play the part of Rick Blaine?",
    options : [
        "John Wayne",
        "Ronald Reagan",
        "Cary Grant",
        "Jimmy Stewart"
    ],
    answer : 1
    },
    {
    question : "The role of Sam was originally meant for a female. Name one of the three African American actresses considered for the part.",
    options : [
        "Lena Horne",
        "Pearl Bailey",
        "Hattie McDaniel",
        "Dorothy Dandridge"
    ],
    answer : 0
    },
    {
    question : "Who is the owner of the Blue Parrot Cafe?",
    options : [
        "Sascha",
        "Ugarte",
        "Senor Ferrari",
        "Major Renault"
    ],
    answer : 2
    },
    {
    question : "Casablanca takes place during what war?",
    options : [
        "World War 1",
        "Korean War",
        "Vietnam War",
        "World War 2"
    ],
    answer : 3
    },
    {
    question : "What is the final line in the movie?",
    options : [
        "Here's looking at you, kid.",
        "Round up the usual suspects",
        "The problems of three little people don't amount to a hill of beans in this crazy world.",
        "Louis, this could be the beginning of a beautiful friendship"
    ],
    answer : 3
    }
];